

Berk Disli

Full Stack Web Developer

Details

Date of birth

19.12.1992

Driving license

В

Profile

Passionate full stack developer, trained in back-end and front-end development. Experienced in engineering and social media industries. Skilled atdesigning, web development, debugging and modifying websites, apps and mobile applications.

Linkedin - GitHub - Portfolio

Holding working permit in Germany and will not need any visa support.

Skills

HTML

CSS

Javascript

React

Angular

Redux

React Native

jQuery

Bootstrap

GiftedChat

MongoDB

SQL

Node.js

Education

Aug 2021 — Mar 2022

Berlin/Germany

Sep 2011 — Jun

Istanbul/Turkey

2016

CareerFoundry

Full Stack Web Development program helps students build API, web and mobile applications. Skills to design and build databases for software applications, create and deploy web API, secure and manage user authentication, to deploy web applications to the cloud. Here is the link to the detailed curriculum of the program.

Isik University

Biomedical Engineering

The program covers fundamental topics of electrical and electronics engineering along with core biomedical engineering courses on systems, physiology, biomaterials, biomechanics, bioinstrumentation, bio-signal processing, medical imaging and bioinformatics.

Development Projects

Aug 2021 — Mar 2022

Berlin/Germany

Web and Mobile Applications

Pokédex API: List of Pokémons

• The web application is designed to provide an overview of all the Pokémon characters.

Chit-Chat: A chat app

• Chit-Chat is a mobile application for fast communication between end users.

To-Do-List App

Languages

English

German

Turkish

 A basic to-do-list app allowing users to add and delete to-dos, edit and mark them as completed.

Meet App: List of developers' events

• The web application is used to see the upcoming events which are set up in Google Calendar.

Movie App: MyFlix

 The website is designed to show the retrieved film data and enable a user profile section. Functions such as logging in, logging out, registering and de-registering users are also integrated.

Employment History

Social Media Specialist - Majorel (01.2021 - present) / Berlin

- Responsible for evaluating online social media content (images, videos, text, etc.), showed in the social media app
- Selecting the content according to the internal policy and criteria
- Removal of inappropriate content in order to ensure a safe experience for users of the application and community
- Maintain a high level of quality in each case

Social Media Specialist - Conectys (11.2018 - 02.2020) / Istanbul

- Screening, monitoring, and approving social media content
- Moderating videos, audio clips and comments in German market for a well-known company

Field Service Engineer - Medisa (01.2016 - 11.2016) / Istanbul

- Designing, testing and implementing new medical procedures as well as modifying products, equipment and devices
- Training staff to use equipment safely and properly and maintaining equipment
- Writing technical reports and documentation